const LakesAndTemples = [
	{
		questionText: 'కేసరి సముద్రం',
		ans: ['మొదటి ప్రోలరాజు'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'రామప్ప చెరువు',
		ans: ['రేచెర్ల రుద్రుడు'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'హనుమకొండ చెరువు',
		ans: ['రుద్రదేవుడు'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'లక్కవరం చెరువు',
		ans: ['గణపతి దేవుడు'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'ఘనాపూర్ చెరువు',
		ans: ['గణపతి దేవుడు'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'పాకాల చెరువు',
		ans: ['జగదల ముమ్మిడి నాయకుడు'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'బయ్యారం చెరువు',
		ans: ['మైలాంబ'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'కుంద సముద్రం',
		ans: ['కుందమాంబ'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'చౌడ సముద్రం',
		ans: ['మాల్యాల చౌడ సేనాని'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'సెట్టికెరయ్య చెరువు',
		ans: ['2వ బేతరాజు'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'స్వయంభూ దేవాలయం',
		ans: ['మొదటి ప్రోలరాజు', 'హన్మకొండ'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'ప్రసన్న కేశవాలయం',
		ans: ['ఎల్లంకి గంగాధరుడు', 'హన్మకొండ'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'సిద్దేశ్వరాలయం',
		ans: ['2వ ప్రోలరాజు', 'హన్మకొండ'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'పద్మాక్షి ఆలయం',
		ans: ['2వ ప్రోలరాజు', 'హన్మకొండ'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'వేయి స్తంభాలగుడి',
		ans: ['రుద్రదేవుడు', 'హన్మకొండ'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'రామప్ప దేవాలయం',
		ans: ['రేచెర్ల రుద్రుడు', 'పాలంపేట'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'పాలంపేట దేవాలయం',
		ans: ['రేచెర్ల రుద్రుడు'],
	},
	// {
	// 	questionText: '',
	// 	ans: [''],
	// },

];

export default LakesAndTemples;
